DEVVA MAULANA

Full Stack Programmer

Pasuruan, August 18th 1996

in linkedin.com/in/devvma

devvamaulana.com

maulanadevva.fitrah@gmail.com

github.com/devvma

(+62) 857 3148 7284 Surabaya, Indonesia

EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Programmer

PT. Sentra Vidya Utama (fulltime)

December 2020 - current | Surabaya, Indonesia

- Manage custom report tasks using jira. Collaborate with the customer support, collect users requirements, then set deadlines. Increased efficiency tasks done by 50%
- Develop custom reports for Siakadcloud product. I created 8 kinds of custom reports for each Universities. Revise the design as requested by the client. I done approximately 30+ report per month
- + Fixing bugs reported by Account Manager and Customer Support. I solved mostly low to medium level bugs.
- + Developing new features on the Student Registration module. I involved in creating One Day Hiring system backend and frontend, adding web push notification and fixing bugs reported by QA, CS and Account Manager
- Create a custom report request guideline document, the content consists of the workflow, list of required documents, and problem mitigation. Reduce 20% of unclear task requirement

Wordpress Developer and Unity Game Programmer Lia S. Associates (fulltime)

October 2018 - July 2020 | Surabaya, Indonesia

- Collaborate with the design team to develop a company profile website. The website is mostly developed with wordpress, i do custom styling, and proofreading web content. I done 10+ wordpress sites
- Optimizing existing Unity mobile games, adding new levels and shrinking game assets file size. The game size is optimized by 20%
- + Developing 2 preschool mobile games using Unity 3D. I created a shape matching game and found the pair.

Full Stack Programmer

Daystudio (freelance)

December 2017 - current | Surabaya, Indonesia

- + Develop responsive landing page website (1 project)
- + Develop company profile website (2 Projects)
- + Develop digital wedding invitation websites (2 projects)
- + Develop Unity 3D games (3 projects)

Web Programmer

PT. Pertamina Persero Mor V (internship)

January 2017 - Februari 2017 | Surabaya, Indonesia

+ Improving talent management system web app. Collaborate with the human resource department to collect user requirements, testing and present. I created import data using excel files, and export talent assessment results to excel files as well.

SUMMARY

Mid-Level Programmer with 5 years programming experience. Self learners, high attention to details, and committed to solving every challenge to make a positive impact. I am equally comfortable working solo as I am in a group setting.

EDUCATION

RS

Computer Engineer
Institut Bisnis dan Informatika Stikom Surabaya
August 2014 - September 2018
Surabaya, Indonesia

SKILLS

Languages:

- + PHP (advance)
- + HTML(advance)
- + CSS (advance)
- Javascript(intermediate)

Frameworks:

- Bootstraps (advance)
- + Laravel(intermediate)

Database:

- + MySql (Intermediate)
- PostgreSql (Intermediate)

Data Visualization: Looker Studio (beginner) Tools: Gitlab, GitHub

CERTIFICATION

Certificate of Competence Programmer Indonesian Professional Certification Authority 2017-2020